{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806894563","data":{"timestamp":" 946806894563"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806904911","data":{"timestamp":" 946806904910"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806911332","data":{"timestamp":" 946806911332"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" cec5306e-3b63-4843-a6af-7d2280d83700"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806913219","data":{"timestamp":" 946806913219"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" cec5306e-3b63-4843-a6af-7d2280d83700"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806913274","data":{"timestamp":" 946806913274"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" cec5306e-3b63-4843-a6af-7d2280d83700"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806924535","data":{"timestamp":" 946806924535"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 51521494-7d07-4bd6-9dc3-f1d117c8579a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806928735","data":{"timestamp":" 946806928734"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 51521494-7d07-4bd6-9dc3-f1d117c8579a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806929880","data":{"timestamp":" 946806929880"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 51521494-7d07-4bd6-9dc3-f1d117c8579a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806932597","data":{"timestamp":" 946806932597"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 51521494-7d07-4bd6-9dc3-f1d117c8579a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806934228","data":{"timestamp":" 946806934228"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 51521494-7d07-4bd6-9dc3-f1d117c8579a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806934411","data":{"timestamp":" 946806934411"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 51521494-7d07-4bd6-9dc3-f1d117c8579a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806937017","data":{"timestamp":" 946806937017"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 51521494-7d07-4bd6-9dc3-f1d117c8579a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" KIANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806937020","data":{"timestamp":" 946806937020"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 51521494-7d07-4bd6-9dc3-f1d117c8579a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806939811","data":{"timestamp":" 946806939811"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 51521494-7d07-4bd6-9dc3-f1d117c8579a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806941059","data":{"timestamp":" 946806941058"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 51521494-7d07-4bd6-9dc3-f1d117c8579a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806943322","data":{"timestamp":" 946806943322"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 51521494-7d07-4bd6-9dc3-f1d117c8579a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806943408","data":{"timestamp":" 946806943408"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 51521494-7d07-4bd6-9dc3-f1d117c8579a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806952693","data":{"timestamp":" 946806952693"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 51521494-7d07-4bd6-9dc3-f1d117c8579a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806968119","data":{"timestamp":" 946806968118"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" b25bff58-2e04-4fe7-bb2b-163ef6e1f54c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806969898","data":{"timestamp":" 946806969898"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" b25bff58-2e04-4fe7-bb2b-163ef6e1f54c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806969985","data":{"timestamp":" 946806969985"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" b25bff58-2e04-4fe7-bb2b-163ef6e1f54c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806986684","data":{"timestamp":" 946806986684"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 18b26cb1-56ab-48f4-8c33-569cd15a0dd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946806993240","data":{"timestamp":" 946806993240"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 18b26cb1-56ab-48f4-8c33-569cd15a0dd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807000475","data":{"timestamp":" 946807000475"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 18b26cb1-56ab-48f4-8c33-569cd15a0dd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807062618","data":{"timestamp":" 946807062618"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 18b26cb1-56ab-48f4-8c33-569cd15a0dd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807072338","data":{"timestamp":" 946807072338"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 18b26cb1-56ab-48f4-8c33-569cd15a0dd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807077666","data":{"timestamp":" 946807077666"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 18b26cb1-56ab-48f4-8c33-569cd15a0dd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807084940","data":{"timestamp":" 946807084939"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 18b26cb1-56ab-48f4-8c33-569cd15a0dd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807092459","data":{"timestamp":" 946807092459"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 18b26cb1-56ab-48f4-8c33-569cd15a0dd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807099237","data":{"timestamp":" 946807099237"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 9e7549ca-7230-4244-abf6-c68b592ea859"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807100378","data":{"timestamp":" 946807100378"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 9e7549ca-7230-4244-abf6-c68b592ea859"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807100436","data":{"timestamp":" 946807100436"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 9e7549ca-7230-4244-abf6-c68b592ea859"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807106046","data":{"timestamp":" 946807106046"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 9e7549ca-7230-4244-abf6-c68b592ea859"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807115140","data":{"timestamp":" 946807115140"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 56d94e4f-6986-4f62-998b-b28251200a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807115371","data":{"timestamp":" 946807115370"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 56d94e4f-6986-4f62-998b-b28251200a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807116071","data":{"timestamp":" 946807116071"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 56d94e4f-6986-4f62-998b-b28251200a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807116171","data":{"timestamp":" 946807116171"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 56d94e4f-6986-4f62-998b-b28251200a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807123558","data":{"timestamp":" 946807123557"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 56d94e4f-6986-4f62-998b-b28251200a5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807171682","data":{"timestamp":" 946807171682"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807183114","data":{"timestamp":" 946807183113"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807200189","data":{"timestamp":" 946807200189"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807206742","data":{"timestamp":" 946807206742"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807244641","data":{"timestamp":" 946807244641"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807251602","data":{"timestamp":" 946807251602"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807256819","data":{"timestamp":" 946807256819"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807264616","data":{"timestamp":" 946807264616"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807273453","data":{"timestamp":" 946807273452"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807279494","data":{"timestamp":" 946807279494"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807284685","data":{"timestamp":" 946807284685"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807290014","data":{"timestamp":" 946807290013"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807301915","data":{"timestamp":" 946807301915"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807306894","data":{"timestamp":" 946807306894"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807312247","data":{"timestamp":" 946807312247"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807317405","data":{"timestamp":" 946807317404"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807352930","data":{"timestamp":" 946807352930"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807359099","data":{"timestamp":" 946807359099"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807365862","data":{"timestamp":" 946807365862"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807373229","data":{"timestamp":" 946807373229"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807380009","data":{"timestamp":" 946807380009"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807385311","data":{"timestamp":" 946807385311"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807390876","data":{"timestamp":" 946807390875"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807396348","data":{"timestamp":" 946807396347"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807402338","data":{"timestamp":" 946807402338"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807408218","data":{"timestamp":" 946807408217"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" d64d2d22-1001-425a-9c10-7cba8c5b21b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807417533","data":{"timestamp":" 946807417533"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807417768","data":{"timestamp":" 946807417767"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807418744","data":{"timestamp":" 946807418742"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807420018","data":{"timestamp":" 946807420017"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807422902","data":{"timestamp":" 946807422902"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807423744","data":{"timestamp":" 946807423744"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807424057","data":{"timestamp":" 946807424057"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807425290","data":{"timestamp":" 946807425289"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807428773","data":{"timestamp":" 946807428773"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807429756","data":{"timestamp":" 946807429756"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807430014","data":{"timestamp":" 946807430014"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807430958","data":{"timestamp":" 946807430957"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807433856","data":{"timestamp":" 946807433856"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807434889","data":{"timestamp":" 946807434889"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807435361","data":{"timestamp":" 946807435361"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807439873","data":{"timestamp":" 946807439872"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807439980","data":{"timestamp":" 946807439979"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ab1dbd5a-775d-4605-9d5d-7d40ca0ae89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807450571","data":{"timestamp":" 946807450571"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" fda68602-d795-4d62-92d5-5727b638c732"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807450794","data":{"timestamp":" 946807450794"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" fda68602-d795-4d62-92d5-5727b638c732"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807451772","data":{"timestamp":" 946807451771"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" fda68602-d795-4d62-92d5-5727b638c732"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807453057","data":{"timestamp":" 946807453056"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" fda68602-d795-4d62-92d5-5727b638c732"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946807455236","data":{"timestamp":" 946807455236"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" fda68602-d795-4d62-92d5-5727b638c732"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946833327722","data":{"timestamp":" 946833327721"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ce3fe5cd-a91d-40ac-8270-54e889f595c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946833349626","data":{"timestamp":" 946833349626"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ce3fe5cd-a91d-40ac-8270-54e889f595c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946833357007","data":{"timestamp":" 946833357006"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ce3fe5cd-a91d-40ac-8270-54e889f595c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946833358710","data":{"timestamp":" 946833358710"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ce3fe5cd-a91d-40ac-8270-54e889f595c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946833369420","data":{"timestamp":" 946833369420"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ce3fe5cd-a91d-40ac-8270-54e889f595c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946833408486","data":{"timestamp":" 946833408485"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ce3fe5cd-a91d-40ac-8270-54e889f595c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946833410185","data":{"timestamp":" 946833410184"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ce3fe5cd-a91d-40ac-8270-54e889f595c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946833413334","data":{"timestamp":" 946833413333"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ce3fe5cd-a91d-40ac-8270-54e889f595c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946833417231","data":{"timestamp":" 946833417231"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ce3fe5cd-a91d-40ac-8270-54e889f595c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946833417327","data":{"timestamp":" 946833417327"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" ce3fe5cd-a91d-40ac-8270-54e889f595c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946833452572","data":{"timestamp":" 946833452572"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 64032699-348d-4aab-a53c-809d860cc16b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946833462151","data":{"timestamp":" 946833462151"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 64032699-348d-4aab-a53c-809d860cc16b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946833480243","data":{"timestamp":" 946833480243"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 64032699-348d-4aab-a53c-809d860cc16b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946833482395","data":{"timestamp":" 946833482394"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_125443"," gameId":" 64032699-348d-4aab-a53c-809d860cc16b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}